http://www.straine.com/privacy-terms

SIGN IN
Privacy We bring big data in small portions to your fingertips.
Straine is a privacy conscious national organization. The following privacy statement explains how we protect visitors’ information gathered via this national Website.If you as a visitor choose to register or submit information to this Website, you agree to the use of such data in accordance with this privacy statement. Please note that this site contains links to other sites, including sites maintained by member partners and alliance partners of Straine, which may not be governed by this privacy statement.If you have any questions regarding this privacy statement or do not feel that your concerns have been addressed, please direct your questions to Webmaster Services using the Contact Us link.TTI Privacy AgreementTarget Training International, Ltd. is a corporation dedicated to improving the quality of life in the workplace through the application of assessments. The company’s mission is to help organizations effectively manage the selection and development of their most valuable asset-people.Your privacy is important to us. This notice explains our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, it is available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Target Training International, Ltd. websites. We do not disclose your personal information to third parties, except to the person or organization that asked you to complete the assessment. Information gathered from persons outside the United States may have their personal data transferred to the USA and to our USA office.When our web site asks for sensitive information such as credit card numbers and expiration dates, that information is encrypted and protected through use of a secure connection using the secure socket layer (SSL) protection.Personal information collected for the processing of a TTI assessment includes: name, e-mail address, gender (for report references only), position/job title, and organization.Personal information collected for credit card purchases includes: full name, address, phone, credit card type, number and expiration date.Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our websites from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our websites are structured to attract anyone under 13.We may use your personal data, i.e. your first name, gender and assessment responses, to produce a personalized profile report about you. Your gender is only used to select the appropriate pronouns for the report. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above. We do not use cookies for collecting user information from the site and we will NOT collect any information about you except that required in producing your profile report and otherwise as described above.To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information (Name, e-mail address, etc.) by contacting the party that asked you to complete the online survey or by sending an e-mail to: support@ttiltd.com. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before making corrections.Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please email us with your contact information at: support@ttiltd.com.BBB Accredited Business since 2006To review information about the Accreditation Standards, including privacy standards, TTI’s reliability report and a complaint page, please click on the seal above.TTI has also self-certified its privacy practices as consistent with U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor principles: Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Access and Accuracy, Security, and Oversight/Enforcement. In order to comply with the European Union’s Safe Harbor Principles, Target Training International, Ltd. has committed to the resolution of complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information as a European Union citizen. If you have any questions or complaints regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at:Target Training International, Ltd17785 N Pacesetter WayScottsdale, AZ 85255Phone: 480-443-1077Web: www.ttiltd.comEmail: support@ttiltd.comComplaints that cannot be resolved directly with our company may be directed to BBB EU Safe Harbor, a dispute resolution procedure administered by the Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. They can be contacted at:Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc.BBB EU Safe Harbor4200 Wilson Boulevard, Suite 800Arlington, VA 22203Phone: 703-276-0100Web: http://www.bbb.org/us/european-union-dispute-resolution/Email: eusafeharbor@council.bbb.orgMore information about the U.S. Department of Commerce US-EU Safe Harbor Framework can be found at http://www.export.gov/safeharbor. You can also review TTI’s current certification status at http://www.export.gov/safehrbr/companyinfo.aspx?id=9589.
Capture theuntapped potentialin your practice. Sign up for a free performance analysis.
Contact Form
Email:
Thank you for contacting us.We will get back to you as soon as possible.
Oops, there was an error sending your message.Please try again later.
Blog  Privacy Terms  Site Map
800-568-7200
EMAIL US
Share by:
